

PROFILE

Harshita Digwani is a certified content writer with 4+ years of experience. She has gained real knowledge of finance, business, and accounts while doing various Top B-School international projects. Her passion, sincerity, presentation, and management skills make her different from others. She wants to secure a responsible career opportunity to fully utilize my skills and competence while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

CONTACT

PHONE: 7023184598

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/h ar shita-digwani-9a76631b2

EMAIL:

harshitadigwani@gmail.com

HARSHITA DIGWANI

Content Writer

WORK EXPERIENCE

K2K IT Support & Solutions Pvt. Ltd. [Technical Writer]

1st January 2024- Present

- Write curative blogs, website homepage content (onpage), and Quora Q&A with SEO-optimized content.
- Handle Chatbot & Answer timely queries for IT Website

Crystaltech Esolutions LLP [Content Writer]

19th December 2023-31st December 2023

- Write SEO blogs for websites (on-page) & third-party websites (off-page) with the right keyword usage.
- Design catchy taglines, well-drafted articles, and luring blogs related to Visa services.

Physics Wallah [Freelancer-Subject Matter Expert]

2nd Dec 2022-30th April 2023

Provide well-defined solutions for CBSE Boards Q & A.

RK Online Marketers [Content Writer]

22nd May 2022 - 18th Dec 2022

- Managed PLR (Private Label Rights, UPLR (Unrestricted Private Label Rights) & Software.
- Prepares Sales Page Copy, JV Copy, Squeeze Page Index File, Free Report, Customer Swipes, JV Swipes, Taglines, Articles, PPTs and Testimonials.
 Proofread the sales pages

Chegg India [Subject Matter Expert]

1st October 2021 – 30th June 2022

 Solve doubts of Economics and maintain CF score above 80% with the maximum satisfaction of the student queries. • Earned Platinum badge, gold badge, and silver badge over the time.

N-Edu Firm [Content Writer]

 3^{rd} August 2021 – 28^{th} December 2021

SKILLS

- Excellent communication skills
- Proactive and intuitive leader
- Achieve deadlines within the time limits
- Innovative presentation skills
- Accounting-related computer knowledge
 Keen learner and observer

CERTIFICATION

- The fundamentals of Digital Marketing by Google Digital Garage
- ICITSS- Orientation Course
- ICITSS-Information Technology
- Graphic Designing Course by Arena Animations
- 2nd National Online Quiz on Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016
- Graphic Designing Course by Alison
- Online Quiz on Double Entry system by SRI RAMAKRISHNA College of
- ARTS and SCIENCE
- Online Quiz on COVID-19 by MyGov

- Online quiz on Insolvency and Bankruptcy Board of India by MyGov
- Certification on Python and Machine Learning Fundamentals
- Managed projects of the top ranked Universities and was rapidly promoted from the junior content specialist position.
- Copywriting
- Prepares social media Blog

Writing Birds [Freelance Writer]

1st August 2021- 5th December 2021(Part time)

- Report Writing
- Handled projects of various Top B-Schools while maintaining the supreme quality of content.

Zomak Solutions [Academic Writer]

1st May 2021 – 31st August 2021

- Managed projects of various Top B-Schools with the highest word count of the month of 85000 words out of 10 employees.
- Gathered customer satisfaction survey and regularly corrected the feedback.

Planet Spark [Public Speaking Expert]

- Taught Public speaking to students digitally
- Learn Product Demonstration skills
- Provide Customer handling Service

EDUCATION

University of Kota

2021-2023

Masters of Commerce

Aggregate-70%

University of Kota

2019 - 2021

Bachelor of Commerce

Meritorious Student with the Highest percentile in 1st year of college (455 marks out of 600), Aggregate- 72%

12th from CBSE Board

Session 2017-18

Bakhshi's Springdales Sr. Sec. School

Aggregate – 72%

Bakhshi's Springdales Sr. Sec. School CGPA – 9.4

10th from CBSE Board

Session 2015-16

Technical Qualification

- MS-Office, Tally, MS Word, MS PowerPoint, MS Access
- Completed ICAI's mandatory Computer Training secured 211.5 marks out of 300.

Professional Qualification

Common Proficiency Test (CPT) by Institute of Chartered Accountant of India in Dec 2018 with a score of 128 marks out of 200.

LANGUAGES

English Hindi Sindhi